The Lawless is a action, thriller film directed by Phillip Guzman.
Two undercover narcotics officers' cover is blown and the
Mexican cartel has kidnapped their families.
To get them back they must do the unthinkable for the next 24 hours.
The rules are simple: No guns, no bombs and no witnesses.
They must become The Lawless.
Ana, played by Natalie Bell.
Gene, played by Eryn Brooke.
Bogota, played by William Burch.
Costello, played by Luis Caldeira.
Frank, played by Jason Riley Hoss.
Victor, played by Denton Blane Everett.
Lucille Frances Lawless  (née Ryan; born 29 March 1968)
is a New Zealand actress and director.
She is best known for her roles as Xena in the television series Xena: Warrior Princess, as D'Anna Biers on the reimagined
Battlestar Galactica series, and Lucretia in the television series Spartacus: Blood and Sand and associated series.
Since 2019, she has starred as Alexa in the television series My Life Is Murder.
Lawless had recurring roles as Diane Lewis-Swanson on the NBC sitcom Parks and Recreation (2012–2014), and
as Countess Palatine Ingrid von Marburg on the WGN America supernatural series Salem (2015).
She also starred as Ruby on the Starz horror-comedy
series Ash vs Evil Dead (2015–2018).
The tone is intense.